http://www.heritagefoodsusa.com/pages/policies

Skip to Content
100% Customer Satisfaction Guaranteed | Questions? Call Us at (718) 389-0985
My shopping cart
Your cart is currently empty.
Menu is closed
Receive $20 off!
As a thank you for signing up for emails, take $20 off your first order with us. Receive exclusive offers, cooking tips, and new arrivals.*We'll never share your email.
HERITAGE FOODS POLICIESShipping Tiers:$1 – $99 = $28 shipping$100 – $199 = $36 shipping$200 – $399 = $46 shipping$399 and over = $46 shipping PLUS RECEIVE A FREE $40 GIFT CERTIFICATE (Fresh Heritage Turkeys not included)Overnight shipping is an additional $25. Thanksgiving Heritage Turkey 2020: Each turkey ships in its own box for $45. Choose your preferred delivery date: Thursday, November 19th, 2020 or Tuesday, November 24th, 2020. Coupons and shipping discounts do not apply to Heritage turkeys. If you ordered any additional items with your turkey, they will ship now, on the next available ship date unless you tell us otherwise in the Order Notes Box at checkout or by calling us at 718-389-0985. All address changes and order cancellations must be received by Thursday, November 5th, 2020.Heritage Foods Loyalty Program• With every 5th order (5th, 10th, 15th, etc.), automatically receive a free Heritage 4lb Pork Loin.  • Starting with your 6th order, you become an Elite Member and a free gift from a sustainable business in our community — from chocolate to honey to organic chili oil and more — will be included in every order placed.  • Starting with your 25th order, you become a Rare Breed Member with access to exclusive, very rare offers not available on our site. A $250 Gift Certificate will be included with every 25th order (25th, 50th, etc.).We are proud to offer free personalized gift cards in any box, gift certificates, and corporate gifting discounts!Shipping Policies:We guarantee 100% satisfaction or your money back.Orders $399 and RECEIVE A FREE $40 GIFT CERTIFICATE! Heritage Turkeys not included.If ordering for a future ship date, please make a note in our Order Notes box provided in the check-out process. Orders are shipped Monday – Thursday. Order deadline is 8AM EST for same day shipments.We ship frozen unless noted otherwise. The product will be shipped with frozen gel packs in insulated containers to preserve the cold chain. For fresh orders please contact our team at (718) 389-0985.You will receive an e-mail when you place your order and again when your order ships containing the tracking number.We ship FedEx 2 Day and Overnight.Our contact information:Heritage Foods: 718-389-0985info@HeritageFoodsUSA.comHeritage Foods217 West 18th StreetPO Box 1219New York, NY 10113 Other Heritage Foods PoliciesIf you don’t feel comfortable sending your credit card information over the Internet we are here for you! Just call (718) 389-0985 and we will take your order over the phone.Unless you have specified a delivery date in the Order Notes box in your Shopping Cart, we will ship as soon as possible via Federal Express. Heritage Foods can ship anywhere in the United States including Alaska and Hawaii.If your shipment was damaged or unacceptable in any way, please contact us immediately. We accept all refund requests anytime. Our number is (718) 389-0985.All orders with the exception of Heritage Turkeys can be canceled with no penalty until 2 days before the shipping date.In order to sign up to receive our emails, you need to provide your e-mail address. You may unsubscribe from our email list at any time. If you want to avoid further messages, you may remove yourself from the mailing list by clicking the unsubscribe button at the bottom of the email.Privacy PolicyThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for HeritageFoods.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing:We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.Heritage Foods will not sell, trade or rent your email or phone number to anyone.Your Access to and Control Over Information:You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via info@HeritageFoodsUSA.com or by phone at 718-389-0985:• See what data we have about you, if any.• Change/correct any data we have about you.• Have us delete any data we have about you.• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security:We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 718-389-0985 or via email at info@HeritageFoodsUSA.com.
Powered by Shopify
x
